<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ciência e Computação</title>
    <link>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/</link>
    <description>Ciência e Computação</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://cienciaecomputacao.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Science and Computing blog</title>
      <link>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/post/boas_vindas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/post/boas_vindas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, hope everyone is well!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am creating this site with a focus on scientific dissemination, so make sure that we all win, you with first-hand information about science and computing. I will post on this site the main subjects about science and computing and I hope that everyone will collaborate with ideas and suggestions or even criticisms and opinions. Unfortunately, there are still many challenges to be overcome. To begin with, the scientific dissemination of what we can do in science with the aid of computing, that is, we will practically start from scratch to understand that computing also does science is not only used for the development and programming of systems. Furthermore, we are used to understanding that science can only be done in more traditional areas such as Biological Science, Chemistry, Physics, Medicine, among others. Something not so visible with computing. However, computing is used in several areas as a support to prove hypotheses that can become theories, through methods such as simulation for example.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow with us the development of our knowledge and help us spread science!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugs and thanks a lot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The blog focuses on scientific dissemination in general and computing. You must be wondering why computing is in science communication? First we have to think that computing is currently fixed in our mind that it is only used for systems development, systems analysis, internet browsing, mobile device programming and even that text written on the computer. However, computing is not just that, there are many more applications behind it than just the common and professional use, known as scientific use,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scientific use of computing can be seen in the most varied sciences, the main one being an interesting area that I dare say, most love astronomy, astrophysics, among others. Through simulations, scientists try to understand how the universe works and not only that, we can, through simulation applied to biology, understand the functioning of bacterial growth or even the evolution of diseases in important cultivars in agriculture. Even areas that use machine learning for classification, regression, clustering, benefit from computing. In addition, areas such as biology, agriculture, mathematics, physics, geography, have seen the importance of computer modeling. For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, computational modeling is an area of ​​computing that aims to solve problems that need multidisciplinary knowledge, such as bioinformatics that needs knowledge in biology, computing and often chemistry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The computational area is so important that it serves as a pillar for many theories that need observations that are only possible by computational means. However, there is not only applied computing, but also pure computing. In which, through research, we seek to develop a new computational method that can be applied in several sub-areas, such as: Machine Learning, Data Science, Security, Pattern Recognition, among others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I invite you to participate in this new world and come and understand at once how computer science is done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big hugs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Subpage</title>
      <link>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/about/subpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/about/subpage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;About subpage&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second About Subpage</title>
      <link>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/about/subpage2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cienciaecomputacao.com/about/subpage2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Second About subpage&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
